The Register to the Betsy Jolas Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1937-2010; Series II
  - Paper, 1
    - Illouz Bugnot, Claire (Daughter), 1982-2003; 72 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      See also Illouz, Gabriel
    - Illouz, Frédéric (Son), 1949-1969; 49 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Illouz, Frédéric, 1970; 80 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Illouz, Frédéric, 1971-1972; 59 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Illouz, Frédéric, 1976-2004, no date; 32 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Illouz, Gabriel (Husband), 1949-1950; 140 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      See also Jolas, Eugene
    - Illouz, Gabriel, 1951-1969; 66 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Illouz, Gabriel, 1970-1993; 113 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Illouz, Gabriel, No date; 152 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - [Illouz?], Leonard "Léo" (Grandson), 2000-2004; 7 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - [Illouz?], Nita, No date; 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      See also Monier-Illouz, Esther
    - Illouz, Michael (Grandson), 1999-2004; 4 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Illouz, Veronique (Mrs. Frédéric Illouz), No date; 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Inamori, Kazuo (Inamori Foundation), 1989-2000; 8 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Institut Française, No date; 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Institut Memoires de l'Édition Contemporain, 1994; 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Institut National de L'Audiovisuel (INA)
      See Couteau, Cati
    - Institut National des Sciences Appliquees de Lyon (INSA), 1986; 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Institut de Recherche et de Coordination Acoustique/Musique (IRCAM)
      See Centre Georges Pompidou
    - Institut Suédois, 1958; 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Studies in American Music, 1974; 4 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Instituut voor Psychoacustica en Elektronische Muziek, 1974-1984; 6 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      See also Centre de Documentation e la Musique Contemporaine (CDMC)
    - International Biographical Centre (Who's Who in Music), 1993; 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - International Congress on Women in Music, 1990; 4 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - International Cultural Engineering and Management
      See Olivier, Philippe
    - International Festival of Contemporary Music Theater, 1999; 6 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - International Folk Music Council
      See Olsen, Louise and Paul Rovsing
    - International Harp Contest in Israel, 1986; 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - International Library of Contemporary Music, 1989-1992; 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - International Society for Contemporary Music (ISCM), 2002; 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      See also Huot, Guy; Levinas, Michaël
    - International Women's Music Festival, 1986; 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Internationaler Wettbewerb für Komponistinnen, 1996; 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Internationales Festival Komponistinnen Heidelberg, 1992; 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Irwin, Wallace Jr., 1983-2003; 11 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Isaacs, Jessica (BBC), 1996; 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - L'Itineraire, 1986-1995; 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      See also Cohen-Levinas, Danielle; Collège International de Philosophie; Levinas, Michaël
    - J., Sylvie, 2001; 3 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jacob, François, 1993; 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jacquet, Mme. Michel, No date; 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jaffe, Shirley, 1993; 3 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jakubowski, Pascale, 1996; 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Japan Art Association (Praemium Imperiale), 1999; 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jarrante, Natacha, 1966-1995, no date; 8 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jaslet-Guezec, Marie-Claude [?], 1995; 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - ?, Jean, 1992-1993; 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - ?, Jean-?, No date; 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - ?, Jeanne [Chevalier?], 2007; 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jeanneret, Lise-Martine, 1965-1968; 7 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jeffcoat, Hollis, 1993; 3 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Les Jeunes Solistes, No date; 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jeunesses Musicales du Canada, 1975; 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jeunesses Musicales de France, 1975; 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      See also de Lavigne, Jean-Pierre
    - Jeunesses Musicales Liège, 1968-1970; 5 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Community Center of Metropolitan New Jersey, 1989; 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Jezouin, Max, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Joachim, Irène, 1993; 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - ?, John, 1981; 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Robert, No date; 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Jolas, Eugene (Father), 1940-1950; 77 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Jolas, Jacques (Uncle), 1986; 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Jolas, Jean, 1976; 3 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Jolas, Maria (mother), 1937-1950; 185 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Jolas, Maria, 1951-1969; 105 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Jolas, Maria, 1976-1985; 32 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Jolas, Maria, No date; 22 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Jolas, Paul, 1988; 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Jolas, Richard (Cousin), 1999; 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Jolas, Tina (Sister) and Char, 1978-1999, no date; 39 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Joo, Hyung-Ki, 1998; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Jorrand, Andre, 1984; 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Joubert, Nathalie, 1997; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Joullieu, Anne-Marie, 1981; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Jouve, Jean-Marc, 1986-1989; 4 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Joyce, Stephen J. and Solange, 1988; 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - ?, Judith, No date; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - The Juilliard School, 1988-1992; 5 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Julong, Gilles, 1987; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Juscik, Steve, 1986; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Jutt, Stephanie, 1977-1979; 6 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kagel, Mauricio, 1999; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kanach, Sharon, 1981; 3 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Karttunen, Anssi, No date; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kashkashian, Kim, 1997; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      See also Société de Musique de Chambre de Lyon
    - Kaufman, Charles, 1986; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      See also Theodore Presser Music
    - Kelemenis, Michel, 2006; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kelley, Dorothea, 1998; 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kelly, John-Edward
      See The Raschèr Saxophone Quartet
    - Kelly, Thomas Forrest
    - Kernis, Aaron Jay, 1983-1988; 8 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kharrat, Abdelkader, 1995; 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kiesgen, Camille (and Charles), 1967; 3 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Kim, Hi Kyung
      See Dugger, Edwin
    - The Kindler Foundation, 1973; 21 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      See also The Concord String Quartet; Theodore Presser Company
    - ?, Kirsten, 1983; 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Kish, Anne, No date; 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Kleiman, Stephen Robert, 1978; 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Klein, Christiane (cousin), 1989-1995; 14 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Klein, Colette, No date; 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Kleinzahler, August, 1999-2005, no date; 39 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Kloepfer, Françoise, 1986; 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Klossowski de Rola, Balthus, 1975-1978; 5 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      See also Académie de France à Rome
    - Knop, Radek, 2000; 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Kobayashi, Marie, 1996; 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Koering, René, 1964-1987; 8 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Kœrner, Jean, 1972-1978; 5 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Koh, Joyce Bee Tuan, 2002; 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Kojima, Yuriko Hase, 1998; 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Kolb, Barbara, 1973-1990; 13 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      See also Wellesley College
    - Det Kongelige Danske Musikkonservatorium (Danish Academy of Music), 1980; 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Konsertfõreningen, 1974; 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Korres, George, No date; 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Kotilainen, Tuula, 1980; 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Koussevitzky Music Foundation, 1974-1976; 8 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Kramer, Andreas, 1991-1996; 5 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Krieg, Pierre-Charles
    - The Kronos Quartet, 1977-1981; 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Krupenye, Grace, 1985; 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Krzywicki, Jan
      See Network for New Music; Theodore Presser Company
    - Kubo, Yoko, 1984; 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Kulturinstitut Komponistinnen gestern-heute, 1988; 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Kumin, Daniel, 1975-1976; 4 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Kurtág, György, 1985; 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Labie, Jean-François, 1994-2001; 10 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      See also D'un Opera de Voyage
    - Lacan, Judith (Daughter of Sylvia Bataille-Lacan), 1994; 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Lachartre, Nicole, 1975; 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Laderman, Ezra, 1991; 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Laferrière, Jérome Julien (aka Fifi), 1985; 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - de La Grange, Henry-Louis, 1982-2006, no date; 22 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      See also Fleuret, Maurice
    - Lainé Galodé, Catherine, 1995-1996; 3 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Laitinen, Juho, 2007; 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Laloë, Frank and Suzanne, 1993-1997, no date; 4 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Lam, Bun-Ching, 1979; 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Lambert, Pierre, 1995; 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Lamy, Anne-Marie, 1987; 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Lanceron, Alain, 1984-2006; 5 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      See also Pathé Marconi
    - Landowski, Marcel, 1970-1997; 5 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Landy, Leigh, 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Lang, Jack, 1984-1997; 13 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      See also Le Ministère de la Culture; Lang, Monique; Légion d'Honneur
    - Lang, Monique, 1992; 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Langlois, Frank, 1988-2007; 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Langlotz, Lukas, 1995-1996; 4 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Laplenie, Michel (?), 1998-2006, no date; 6 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Larbi, Hacène, No date; 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Larquié, André, 1995; 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Larroche, Mireille
      See La Péniche Opéra
    - Lauba, Christian, 1987; 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Laurence, Elizabeth, 1999; 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - de Lavigne, Jean-Pierre, 1977-1979; 4 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Lawey, Nicole, 2000; 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Lazarevitch, Francois, 2005; 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Lazkano, Ramon, 2006; 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - The League of Composers, Inc., 1949; 2 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Lèandre, Joëlle, 1992, no date; 9 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Leber, Jean
      See Octuor de Paris
    - Lecat, Jean-Philippe
    - Leclair, François-Hugues, 1996; 2 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Lecompte, Michel, 1986; 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Ledoux, Michel, 1990; 2 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Leduc, Alphonse
      See Alphonse Leduc Éditeurs de Musique
    - Leduc, C.A.
    - Leduc, François, 1982-1995; 19 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      See also Alphonse Leduc Éditeurs de Musique; Heugel et Cie.; United Music Publishers
    - Leduc, Jean, 1981-1999, no date; 90 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      See also Alphonse Leduc Éditeurs de Musique; American String Teachers Association; Composers Recordings, Inc.; Personnalité de l'Année; Theodore Presser Company; United Music Publishers
    - Leduc, Sophie, No date; 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Lee, Noël, 2002; 5 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - de Leeuw, Tom, 1987-1995; 4 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Lefanu, Nicola, 1996-1997; 5 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Lefort, Françoise, No date; 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Légion d'Honneur, 1996; 5 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      See also Lang, Jack
    - Legris, Philippe, 1985; 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Leguay, Jean-Pierre, 1987-1990; 5 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Leguay, Laetitia, 2004; 3 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Lehry, Robin, 1999; 4 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Lejet, Edith, 1996-2001; 2 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Lejeune, Dominique, 1984; 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Leman, Gérard, 1975-1986; 3 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Lemer, Jean-Louis, 1990-1992; 6 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Le Moigne, Philippe, 1991-1993, no date; 7 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Lentrodt, Ursula, 1970; 4 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Leon, Georges, 2002; 1 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Léonard, Paul-Alain, 1974-2000; 4 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Lerche-Lerchenborg, Louise, 1986-2002; 12 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Leriche-Andrieu, Françoise, 1985; 6 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Le Roux, Francois, 2005; 1 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Leroux, Philippe, 1996; 1 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Leroy, Sylvie, 1997-2001; 8 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Le Roy, Thierry, 1995; 1 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Leroy-Chevalier, Michèle, 1984; 5 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Leser, Marie-Thérèse, 1968; 2 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Lessing, Walter, 1969-1970; 4 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Lesur, Daniel, 1966-1983; 5 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - de Leuchtenberg, Anna [?], No date; 2 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Level, Pierre-Yves, 1990; 1 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Levering, Arthur, 1999; 1 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Lévi-Strauss, Claude, 1993-1999; 2 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Lévi-Strauss, Monique, 1993-2006; 9 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Levin, Robert, 2005; 2 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      See also Harvard University; Société de Musique de Chambre de Lyon
    - Levinas, Michaël, 1984-2008, no date; 6 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      See also L'Itinéraire; International Society for Contemporary Music
    - Levine, Jesse, 1989-2000; 2 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Levine, Renée, 1981-1995; 6 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Levinson, Gerald (Jerry), 1997-1998; 3 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Levy, Jacqueline, 1986; 1 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      See also Schmidt, André
    - Lewis, Daniel, 1991; 3 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      See also Thomson, William; University of Southern California
    - Lewis, Robert Hall, 1976-1994; 4 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Leymarie, Jean, 1977-1993; 3 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Libération, 1986; 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Librairie Larousse, 1970; 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - The Library of Congress (USA), 1976-1992; 8 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Liebermann, Rolf, 1975-1988; 6 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Liebermann, Hélène, No date; 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Liebert, Georges, 1991; 3 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Ligeti, György, 1994; 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Lignerolles Librarie Musicale, 1987; 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Lili Boulanger Memorial Fund, Inc., 1985-1986; 4 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Liptak, David
      See Wicks, Christopher
    - Liron, Marie-Thérèse, 1978; 3 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Little, Lester K., 2005; 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Livingston, Guy, 1991-1996; 6 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Livio, Antoine, 1997; 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Lockwood, Lewis
    - Lombard, Alain, 1993; 4 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Londeix, Jean-Marie, 1982-1997; 6 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      See also Leduc, François; Association des Saxophonistes de France
    - Longchamp, Jacques, 1987; 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Lontano Music Ensemble
      See United Music Publishers
    - Lorent, Catherine, 1991; 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Lorenzo, Vioque, 1977; 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Loriod, Jeanne, 1977; 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Loriod, Yvonne (Wife of Olivier Messiaen), 1981-1996; 11 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Lotti, Federica, 2000; 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Loudin, Carlo [?], 1982; 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - The Louisville Orchestra, 1959; 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Louvrier, Alain, 1987-1993; 14 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      See also Conservatoire National Supérieur de Musique de Paris; Wajyma, Hiroko
    - Lorano, Maguy, 1982; 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Love, Josephine Harreld, 1969; 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Lowenstamm, Hugo, 1984; 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Lumbroso, Pierre, 1988; 1 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Lumbroso, Roland (cousin), 1993; 3 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Lutoslawski, Witold, 1964; 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Lyon, Mme. ?, 1950-1970; 4 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Lytle, Cecil
      See University of California, San Diego
    - Mabry, Drake, 1985; 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Machart, Renaud, 1993; 4 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Mâche, François-Bernard, 1995-2004; 3 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Mackey, Lynne, 1990; 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Maeght, Aimé, No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Maghini, Ruggero, 1974, no date; 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Maguieu, Frédérique, 1973; 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Magyar Rádió és Televizió (RTF Hongroise), 1958; 4 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Maheu, Isabelle, 1992; 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Maheu, Jean, 1977-1986; 6 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      See also Le Ministère de la Culture; Radio France; Le Secrétaire d'Etat
    - Maison des Conservatoires, No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Maison de la Culture - Amiens
      See Ferrari, Luc
    - Maison de la Radio, 1976; 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Malec, Ivo, No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Mandanici, Marcella, 1990; 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Maney, B, No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Mann, Lucy
      See Wajyma, Hiroko; Éditions Salabert
    - Mannes Trio, 1988; 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      See also Kaufman, Charles; Walsh, Diane; Wajyma, Hiroko
    - Manoury, Philippe, 1993-2002; 3 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Mantovani, Bruno, 2007; 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Marbe, Myriam, 1977; 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Marchesseau, Daniel, No date; 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - [Marcotte?], Nicolas-Alexandre, 1994; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - ?, Margot [Levy?], No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Marie France (Magazin), 1985; 3 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Markovits, Joséphine, No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Marmouset, Véronique, 2000; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Marquis Who's Who, Inc., 1985; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Marrey, B., 1968; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Marsh, Roger, 1996, no date; 5 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Laurent, 2001; 4 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Scott, No date; 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Stéphane
    - Martin, Sylvain, 1986; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Martinez, Sofia, No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Martinot, Thierry, 1993; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Martinoty, Jean-Louis, 1991; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Martinson, Roger, 1975; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Marty, Jean-Pierre
    - Mason, Raymond, 1993; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Le Masque et La Lyre, 1992; 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Masse, Alan, 1990; 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Masse, Pierre, 1970; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Masse, Isabelle, 1999; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Massin, Brigitte, 1974-1995; 3 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Masson, Diego and Luis, 1987; 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Massot, Louis, 1987; 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Mathews, Harry, 1993; 10 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Mayolle, Pierre-Henri, 1993-1997; 4 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Mazeron, Lilane, 1972, no date; 4 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - McNabb, Michael, 1975; 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mécénart (Concourse de chant Ninon Vallin), 1986; 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mecklenburgh Opera, 1995, no date; 5 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Meet the Composer, Inc., 1989; 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Melnick, Jacqueline
      See Mount Holyoke College
    - Memed, Orhan, 2006-2007; 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mens, Catherine, 1996; 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Menil Foundation Inc., 1976; 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mercier, Thierry, No date; 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mergier, Pierre, 1993; 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Meric, Maurice, 1975-1976; 3 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Merlet, Dominique, 1993, no date; 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Merryman, Marjorie, 1987-1995; 6 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mesare, Jeanne and Robert, 1966; 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mesnard, ?, 1968; 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mesplé, Mady, 1965-1988; 12 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Messiaen, Olivier, 1971-1981, no date; 34 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      See also Association Orgue Hommage à Messiaen; Kulturinstitut Komponistinnen gestern-heute; Loriod, Yvonne
    - Metz-Centre Européen pour la Recherche Musicale, 1981-1989; 4 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Metzelaan, Helen, 1983-1984; 4 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Meuge, Pierre-Stéphane, 1993; 1 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Meyer, Ph. [?], 1992; 1 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Meyer, Vincent, No date; 5 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Mexandeau, Louis, 1981 [?]; 2 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - ?, Michael [McNabb?], No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Miedzynarodowy Festiwal Muzyki Współczesnej, 1974; 5 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Migot, André, 1966; 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Mihalovici, Marcel, 1959; 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1979-1994, no date; 12 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Milhau, Laurent, 1996; 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Milhaud, Darius, 1954-1981; 82 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      See also Amis de l'œuvre de Darius Milhaud
    - Milhaud, Madeleine, 195[?]-2002; 19 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Millet, Florence, 1999-2000; 2 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Mills College, 1979; 5 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Mills, Vlasta (née Balkova), 1992, no date; 2 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Milo, Leon, 1992; 1 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Ministère des Affaires Culturelles
      See Landowski, Marcel; Le Ministère de la Culture
    - Le Ministère des Affaires Étrangères, 1974-1975; 3 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Ministère des droits de la femme, 1985; 3 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      See also Fondation Yehudi Menuhin
    - Le Ministère de la Culture (Various), 1972-2003, no date; 66 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      See also Donnedieu de Vabres, Renaud; Fleuret, Maurice; Host, Pierre; Landowski, Marcel; Lang, Jack; Lang, Monique; Larquié, André; Maheu, Jean; Trautmann, Catherine
    - Ministère des Relations Extérieures, 1984; 1 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Le Ministre [de la Culture?], 1976; 1 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Mintchev, Gueorgui, No date; 2 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Mion, Philippe, 1991-1992; 6 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Miroglio, Francis, 1977-1995; 5 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Miroglio, Thierry, 1993-1995; 5 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Mitchell, Brenda, 1985-2001; 2 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Mitchell, Joan, 1968-1993; 13 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Mittelberg, Zuka, 1998; 10 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Mitterrand, François, 1981-1994; 12 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Moe, Lawrence, 1984; 4 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      See also Nin-Culmell, Joaquin
    - Moll, Phillip, 2004; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Monaco, Principauté de (Government), 1989-1995; 9 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      See also Princesse Caroline de Monaco; Fondation Prince Pierre de Monaco
    - Le Monde de la Musique, 2006; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Monino, Frederic, 2000; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Monk, Craig, 1993-1994; 4 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Monier-Illouz, Esther (granddaughter), 1985-2004 [?], no date; 19 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Monnet, Marc, 2005, no date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Monrosty, Josiane, No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Montassier, Gérard
    - Monty, Nicolas, 2002; 2 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Moody Books, 1999; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Moon, Eugene (Gene)
      See Theodore Presser Company; Koussevitzky Music Foundation
    - Mortari, Luisa, 1993; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Mortimer, Mathilde (Duchess of Argyll), 1973 [?]; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Morton, Laurence, No date; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Mouffetard, Nouveau Theatre, 1987; 1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      See also Simpson, David
    - Mouillere, Jean, 1989; 5 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Mount Holyoke College, 1979; 3 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Mouvement Janácek
      See Erismann, Guy
    - Mugar Memorial Library (Boston University)
      See New York Public Library
    - Muller, Anne, 1994-1995; 9 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Muller, Jacqueline, 1987-2000; 5 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      See also Diapason; Radio France
    - Murail, Françoise and Tristan, 1993-1998, no date; 3 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Muraro, Roger, 2007; 4 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Musée d'Orsay, 1987; 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Musical America, 1989; 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Musidisc SA, 1997; 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Musique Nouvelle en Liberté, 1992-1994; 4 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Musique Plus, 1976; 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Muzički Biennale Zagreb, 1967; 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Muzzik, 2000; 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - My, Dominique, 1993; 5 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Nagano, Kent, 1988-2005; 6 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Nagel, Tom, 1988; 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Nakatani, Yoshie, 2008; 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Naohachi, Usami, 1988; 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Naquet, Pierre Vidal, 2006; 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Narboni, François, 1998-1999, no date; 6 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Nash Ensemble of London
      See Freedman, Amelia
    - ?, Natacha, 1966; 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - The National Institute of Arts and Letters